{
    "subject": "resource/Princesse_Tam-Tam",
    "predicate": "property/producer",
    "object": "Arys Nissotti",
    "human_readable": "Princesse Tam-Tam was produced by Arys Nissotti.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9156776666641235,
            "question": "Who produced Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9147170782089233,
            "question": "What other works has Arys Nissotti produced besides Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8630567789077759,
            "question": "Name a work produced by Arys Nissotti."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8175331354141235,
            "question": "Is Arys Nissotti a producer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8056833744049072,
            "question": "What is the name of the person who produced Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7622949481010437,
            "question": "Who created the work titled Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7474616169929504,
            "question": "What is Arys Nissotti known for producing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5986113548278809,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the production process of Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5349164605140686,
            "question": "Is there any information available about the inspiration behind Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42796164751052856,
            "question": "What type of creative work is Princesse Tam-Tam?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Princesse Tam-Tam was produced by Arys Nissotti.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1288_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about the inspiration behind Princesse Tam-Tam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1288_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the production process of Princesse Tam-Tam?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1288_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Arys Nissotti known for producing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1288_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1288_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents indicates that the film \"Princesse Tam-Tam\" was indeed produced by Arys Nissotti, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}